coolutils.com 2019-06-18

# Privacy Policy For CoolUtils Apps

The privacy of our users is very important to us. We do our best to make their experience with coolutils as good as possible. Like most website operators, we collect non-personally-identifying information (typically the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request). Our sole purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how our visitors use www.coolutils.com. 

We don't ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. For example, all our free online converters do not ask for your name or email or any personal info. However, we need you info to process orders and generate keys for our programs. We store personal information (names and emails) in an encrypted way on our server. We do not share your personal information with anyone except to resend the keys or inform about new upgrades. All the other personal information gathered during the purchase of CoolUtils programs is not stored on our servers as the payments are collected and processed by PayPro Global Inc. 

PayPro Global Inc. gathers all the information needed to process online payments on our behalf. They have implemented technology and security policies, rules and measures to protect the personal data that they get under their control from: unauthorized access, improper use, alteration, unlawful or accidental destruction, accidental loss. Please, learn their Privacy Policy at <https://payproglobal.com/compliance-data-privacy/>

### Privacy Policy Changes

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time, though the changes will be minor. All the new changes are always available to public view in the updated version of Privacy Policy on this page. Your continued use of our site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of the change.
